Hmm.
Um... Ah, nah.
Mm... Ah.
Yeah.
Goin' through the 'bot wash
Goin' through the robot wash
Come on, y'all
And sing it with me
'Bot wash
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa
'Bot wash, yeah
Hmm!
Oh...
Ah.
Oh!
Hey, I'm Elzar.
Welcome to the show.
You know, you don't have
to drive all the way to Neptune
for great Neptunian food.
Today, we're gonna kick it up a notch
as I show you how to fricassee
a mouthwatering Neptunian slug.
Whoo-whee!
Now, while you're greasing the pan
and preheating your oven to 3,500 degrees,
you're gonna separate the yolk
from your genetically enhanced eggplant,
and then give the whole thing a good blast
from your spice weasel.
Bam!
Hey, what you watching?
Uh, nothing.
Is that a cooking show?
No, of course not.
It was, uh...
Porno. Yeah, that's it.
Bender, I didn't know you liked cooking.
That's so cute.
Aw, it's true.
I've been hiding it for so long.
It's okay, Bender. I like cooking, too.
Pansy.
Of course, your most important ingredient
Is this baby right here,
the Neptunian slug.
You can get it in a can,
but to really do things right,
you got to strangle yourself a fresh one.
Now this is why you always want to use
cast iron cookware.
Bender, mon,
it has come to my attention
that this company has been paying you
to do nothing but loaf about on the couch.
You call that a couch?
I demand a pillow.
I'm sorry, but if you want
to continue drawing a salary,
you've got to do more than watch
the cooking shows all day.
Hmm...
You're gonna be the ship's cook?
Yeah. We're gonna kick it up a notch.
Bam!
I know you like cooking shows,
but you're a robot.
You don't even have a sense of taste.
Honey, I wouldn't talk about taste
if was wearing a lime green tank top.
Bam!
So this is little Neptune.
Yep. Every chef knows this is the place
to get exotic gourmet ingredients.
Among other things.
Come on, man!
Don't hold out on me like this!
Psst. You want to buy organ?
Fresh and cheap ready for transplant.
- Ooh, what's this?
- Ah, it's X-ray eye.
See through anything.
Wait a minute. This says Z-ray.
"Z" is just as good. In fact, it's better.
It's two more than "X."
Hmm, I can see where
that would be an advantage.
Do you take cash?
Fry, you have to be more careful.
You're not in the 20th century anymore.
You don't know how things work here.
I'm not a little kid, Leela.
I grew up in this city.
These are my people.
- What up?
- Word.
See?
Wow! You guys sell
every kind of meat here except human.
What? You want human?
What's this spice for?
That's powdered swamp root.
Makes you irresistible
to the opposite sex.
Oh, that's ridiculous.
I'll take two pounds.
Hey, buddy.
I'm looking for fresh slug.
- Yellow or purple?
- Whatever.
The purple one
causes terrible nightmarish diarrhea.
Yeah, yeah, either one's fine.
Hey, have you seen Fry?
Now that you mention it,
I do have trouble
breathing underwater sometimes.
I'll take the gills.
Yes, gills.
Then, uh, you don't need
lungs anymore, is right?
Can't imagine why I would.
Lie down on table.
I take lungs now, gills come next week.
Nurse!
Let's do it.
You may feel small pain.
Hyah!
Thank you.
What the hell were you doing?
I warned you to stay away from those guys.
I'm capable of making
my own decisions, Leela.
Did you ever stop to think
I might be happier with gills?
Good news, everyone.
Uh-oh, I don't like the sound of that.
You'll be making a delivery
to the planet Trisol.
Here it comes.
A mysterious world in the darkest depths
of the forbidden zone.
Thank you, and good night.
Uh, Professor, are we even
allowed in the forbidden zone?
Why, of course. It's just a name.
Like the Death Zone
or the Zone of No Return.
All the zones have names like that
in the Galaxy of Terror.
- Uh, Professor...
- Off you go.
Pleasant trip.
Hey, Bender
- How's dinner coming?
- Almost ready.
Ah, now for a dash of salt.
Uh-oh.
Listen, this is Bender's first meal
and he's a little sensitive.
So let's be supportive, okay?
- Right.
- Yeah, okay.
Oh, dear God!
Ugh. That's the saltiest thing
I've ever tasted.
And I once ate a big heaping bowl of salt.
Bender, is this salt water?
That's salt with water in it,
if that's what you mean.
My vision's fading.
I think I'm gonna die.
There was nothing wrong with that food.
The salt level was 10% less
than a lethal dose.
Uh-oh, I shouldn't have had seconds.
Okay, Fry, here's the package to deliver.
And for once in your life, be careful.
This is my first visit
to the Galaxy of Terror
and I'd like it to be a pleasant one.
Ow!
Don't touch anything or talk to anyone.
Just go to the palace,
drop it off and come right back.
Geez, will you lay off?
I was delivering things
before you were born.
I think I know what I'm doing.
Oh, stupid slug.
I've never been so thirsty.
Oh, come on, go down already.
Hello? Anybody home?
Ah...
The royal bottle is empty!
You drank our emperor!
No, it wasn't me.
You assassinated him!
I didn't mean to.
He just looked so cool and refreshing.
I'm sure he was.
But now he's gone,
and your fate is sealed.
All hail the new emperor!
Hail! Hail! Hail!
So after I specifically
asked you not to touch anything,
you drank a bottle of strange blue liquid.
It could have been poisonous acid.
It could have been, but chances were
equally good it was an emperor.
Excuse me, Your Majesty.
I am Murg, the high priest.
If I might interject?
You might.
I humbly advise that, as your first act,
you choose a capable prime minister.
I suggest Gorgak, the previous appointee.
I will be a forceful
and effective administrator.
You know, Fry, I've often thought
about becoming a prime minister.
I gotta go with Bender.
Yes! In your face, Gorgak!
That's it, Fry.
As your captain,
I order you back to the ship.
You are in way over your head.
Gee, you think so, Captain?
I'd better check with my prime minister.
Stay the course, pal.
Your Highness, a package came for you.
Hey, thanks.
Wow, this got here just in time.
This is Your Majesty's harem.
You may choose any of these maidens
to be your royal consort.
Uh... Uh, uh, uh... How about that one?
Oh! I didn't realize Your Majesty
was into that sort of thing.
On second thought, uh, I'll take that one.
Hey, whatever you say.
I'm not here to pass judgment.
Does anyone else think it's odd
that a shiftless, 25-year-old delivery boy
could drop out of the sky,
kill the emperor
and be rewarded instead of punished?
You don't have to beat
around the bush, Leela.
We all know who you're talking about.
Me, right?
Uh, I don't think
there's anything to worry about.
These people seem really mild-mannered.
They are mild.
In fact, you're soaking in one right now.
You touched me in ways
I've never been touched before.
Ah, there you are, Your Majesty.
It's time to begin preparing
for tomorrow's coronation ceremony.
A fancy dress gala?
I'll wear my formal shell.
Fry will be enthroned tomorrow
at the setting of the three suns,
when we Trisolians
enter our nocturnal phase.
There won't be a lot
of long-winded speeches, will there?
Only one.
The absolutely flawless recitation
from memory of the royal oath...
by you.
Will there be cake?
- Yeah, I know.
- Hi!
- There you go.
- Mmm!
And now, get ready to laugh
till your sides leak
with our planet's foremost
political satirist, Florp.
So what is the deal with people
from under the orange sun?
They're all...
But us guys from under
the red sun, we're like...
Right? Am I right?
Oh, yeah, he's right.
Fry, I have to talk to you.
You're in terrible danger.
You see emperor Plon here?
He met his end
when he was drunk by Emperor Strug.
And before he could even wipe his mouth,
Strug was drunk by Shwab.
- So?
- Look at all these guys.
Do you have any idea what
the average length of their reigns was?
Uh... 80,000 years?
No, one week.
Damn. I knew you wouldn't have asked
unless it was really high or really low.
Every emperor ascended to power
by assassinating the previous one.
And guess who's next?
Well, at least my assassin
will get what's coming to him.
You're in tremendous danger, you idiot!
Half these emperors
were drunk at their own coronation.
Hey, I plan on having
a few brewskis myself.
No, they were assassinated.
In fact, the law says
you'll be killed on the spot
if you fail to recite
the oath from memory.
Yeah, I was gonna
thumb through that later.
That is completely reckless.
Don't you ever think ahead?
Hell, no.
If I stopped to think ahead,
I wouldn't be emperor,
and I wouldn't even be here
in the year 3000.
It's just like the story
of the grasshopper and the octopus.
All year long, the grasshopper
kept burying acorns for winter
while the octopus mooched off
his girlfriend and watched TV.
But then the winter came
and the grasshopper died,
and the octopus ate all his acorns
and also, he got a race car.
Is any of this getting through to you?
Ugh. I give up.
You're gonna get yourself killed,
and this time,
I won't be able to save you.
Who asked you to?
I told you a hundred times
to stop treating me like a baby.
Now go. Go gather your nuts,
you nagging grasshopper.
That's it! I'm never helping you again.
If anyone except you needs me,
I'll be in the ship.
I'll be fine.
It's not like anyone's gonna drink me.
Quit it.
People of Trisol,
it is my honor to present
your new emperor.
What up?
Stick to the oath.
Right.
I, Fry, who drank Bont the Viscous,
who drank Ungo the Moist,
who guzzled Zorn the Stagnant,
who slurped Hudj the Dewy,
who enjoyed a soup composed
principally of Throm the Chunky,
do solemnly swear
to rule with honor and...
insanity...
uh, integrity.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
I now present you
with your royal unisex robe.
Long live Fry the Solid!
Hey, look, the suns are setting.
I can finally switch to hard liquor.
Ah.
Check out the glowing freaks.
It's beautiful.
Hey, what's that?
The emperor Bont!
He's still alive!
Of course I'm alive.
Now cut this creep open and drain me out.
My tummy hurts.
They're over here.
They're running up the stairs.
Shut up, you.
Let us in!
Fry must die so that bont may live.
What am I gonna do?
We've gotta get the emperor
out of your body before they kill you.
Relax, Fry.
I'll simply spin you
in a high-speed centrifuge,
separating out
the denser fluid of His Highness.
But won't that crush my bones?
Oh, right, right, with the bones.
I always forget about the bones.
Hey, why don't you just sweat him out?
Forget it.
As emperor, I refuse to be dripped out
through somebody's armpit.
I could vomit or urinate.
Would you feel better about that?
Slightly. But my favorite so far
is the bone crushing.
What about crying?
That's a great idea. Crying.
Fine. That or the bone one.
Keep it up, men.
The veneer is starting to peel.
Oh, dear.
It's no use.
I wanna cry, but I'm just too macho.
I'll make you cry, buddy.
You're a pimple on society's ass
and you'll never amount to anything.
What do you mean?
I was emperor of a whole planet.
Good point.
But here's a disturbing reminder,
everyone you knew or loved
in the 20th century is dead.
- These things happen.
- Argh.
Okay, Fry, grab a Kleenex for this one
'cause there's no god
and your idiotic human ideals
are laughable.
Whew.
That's a load off my mind.
Man, I guess it's harder than I thought
to make someone cry.
You did your best, Bender.
Up yours, bimbo!
Let's face it, we're in hot butter here.
We should call Leela for help.
Cram it, lobster.
But that is a good idea. I'll go call her.
Eh, she'll never help me.
She's still mad that I told her
never to help me.
Come on, Leela's not the type
to hold a grudge.
Collect call from...
I'm not giving my name
to a machine!
I'll accept.
Fry's in trouble and he needs help.
Now, I don't like you
and you don't like me...
- I like you.
- You do?
Ah. Look, are you gonna help or not?
I don't know why I should.
I mean, after what he...
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What is it you like best about me?
Is she coming?
I'm not sure, but I do know
that she likes my in-your-face attitude.
What the hell is that?
It's the Juice-A-Matic 4000.
It'll strain my juices from you
while filtering out the pulp.
By which I mean your shredded remains.
Of course. Why didn't I think of that?
This is the saddest day of my life
and I still can't cry.
Wait a second.
Here comes Leela!
Oh, no. They have her totally outnumbered.
I can't believe it.
She's risking her life for me
after the way I treated her?
Oh, I don't deserve this.
I feel terrible.
You do? Hmm...
- Is she all right?
- Uh, I don't know.
Perhaps I'll look out this window.
Oh, dear God in heaven!
They're swarming all over her!
No! no!
What are you talking about, Bender?
She's...
Mm.
There's strapping her to the juicer!
Oh, they're putting some ice cubes
in the glass under it.
This can't be happening!
It can, and for all you know, it is.
Oh, I'm sorry, Fry.
She's dead.
All Leela ever wanted to do was help me
And I was too proud
and stupid to accept it.
I wish I had died instead of her.
What are you talking about?
Leela! You're alive!
Of course I'm alive.
I told Fry you were dead
so he would cry out the emperor,
but you had to go
and wreck it by surviving.
We only got two drops.
What the...
It's only a matter of time now.
I'll handle this.
Listen, Fry,
I think I can get us out of this
if you're willing to let me help you.
Thanks, Leela.
From now on, I'll take all the help
you're willing to give.
I know you just want what's best for me.
Ow! What was that for?
Hey, come on!
That hurt!
I know.
Amy, get the bottle.
Ow!
Oh, now I understand.
Come on. Everybody help out Fry.
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Thanks, everybody.
I love you all.
You guys are true... Oh!
Cut it out, Bender. That's a tender area.
How we doing, Amy?
Great. We're one-tenth of the way there.
Okay, it's your turn.
Hey, wait a minute. Who are you?
I'm the emperor.
Thanks for crying me out.
Oh, you're welcome.
Hey, save some for me!